

Lubov May O in

Front End Developer San Leandro, CA liubov.mayorova@gmail.com

Skills

Programming Languages

- Javascript (ES6) / jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, Sass, HTML DOM
- Working experience with Async/Await, Promises API, DOM traverse, Event Listeners.
- API: Async/await, fetch, working with multiple fetch request

Libraries and Frameworks

- · React, Redux, Bootstrap
- Functional and Class Components, Mapping Components, React State, Handling Events, Lifecycle methods, Hooks, React Forms. Building apps using Flexbox and Grid.

UI Design

 Basic knowledge of UI design best practices. Created fully responsive web applications with mobile-first concept in mind

Tools and Platforms

• Git, Heroku, Firebase, npm

WordPress, PHP

 Developed fully functional web sites using Wordpress and PHP.

Debugging

· Chrome Inspector.

Accomplishments

All projects listed below were developed by me.

- Built personal portfolio website using plain HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Grid.
- Created Bookshelf app with React and third-party API.

BIO

I have over 2.5 years of experience as a Front End Developer. I started my career as an intern in a digital agency by developing fully functional responsive websites for a wide variety of businesses. I gained a lot of knowledge and experience working in a fast-paced environment. I am excited to move deeper into programming, build apps rather than websites, and I love using the latest technologies. I'll be happy to get on board with a React front-end developers team who value clean quality code. While I love JavaScript and React, I am also a passionate learner and always willing to learn new frameworks and languages.

Work Experience

Nika Digital Agency, Sep 2017 - July 2020

Responsible for developing fully functional responsive websites. Created more than 20 websites and landing pages with HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, PHP and Wordpress. Created and maintained front-end code and documentation standards. Responsible for optimizing images and minifying CSS and JavaScript. Cross-Browser development. Responsive and Mobile design.

Further Education

Udacity (React Nanodegree Program)

March 2021 - In progress

Scrimba (The Frontend Developer Career Path)

July 2020 - May 2021

Udemy (The Complete React Developer Course (w/ Hooks and Redux))

December 2019 - January 2020

Udemy (The Modern JavaScript Bootcamp)

November 2019 - January 2020

Formal Education

Moscow State University of service

Hospitality and tourism service manager 2002-2005

Powered by CakeResume